[WISTFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you so much
for paying
for my mother's surgery.
It's the least I could do.
[WISTFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Where's Hannah?
Oh. They already left, sir.
[MUSIC BUILDING]
[EXCITING MUSIC PLAYING]
They just left a while ago.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, sir!
Let us assist you, sir!
We'll give you all
the assistance you need, sir!
[EXCITING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DANIEL] Hannah!
Hannah!
Stop the car!
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
Don't go to Korea.
Only the Chairman
is going to Korea
after we visit my mother
in the hospital.
Great.
Because I'm staying here.
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm half Filipino, Hannah.
And I hated it all of my life.
But because of you...
[GIGGLING]
[BANG ON DOOR]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
...I fell in love
with my other side.